<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:webfeeds="http://webfeeds.org/rss/1.0" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>jfribeiro.dev</title>
    <link>https://magoninho.github.io/blog</link>
    <atom:link href="https://magoninho.github.io/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <description>Blog about Programming, Tutorials, Guides, some off-topic subjects and tech in general</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 22:19:26 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en</language>
    <generator>Lume v2.5.1</generator>
    <item>
      <title>A very useful guide on how to use yt-dlp</title>
      <link>https://magoninho.github.io/blog/posts/very-useful-guide-on-yt-dlp/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://magoninho.github.io/blog/posts/very-useful-guide-on-yt-dlp/</guid>
      <content:encoded>
        <![CDATA[<p>I've been using <code>yt-dlp</code> for a long time and it has been very useful for me in the daily basis. When I want to download a video or a song from youtube, it really comes in handy to have a tool that is not bloated with ads and fake download buttons like those youtube downloader clients we see over the internet.</p>
<!-- more -->
<p><code>yt-dlp</code> is a powerful tool packed with features, but that’s also what makes it <strong>challenging to learn</strong>. It offers a wide range of functionalities, many of which go unused by the average user. Most people simply want to download videos as MP4 or songs as MP3, without having to navigate its extensive options.</p>
<p>My goal is to summarize some commands that I think are the most useful for the daily basis.</p>
<h2 id="installation" tabindex="-1"><a href="https://magoninho.github.io/blog/posts/very-useful-guide-on-yt-dlp/#installation" class="header-anchor">Installation</a></h2>
<p>You can <a href="https://github.com/yt-dlp/yt-dlp?tab=readme-ov-file#installation">visit the official github repository</a> to find the steps on how to install it.</p>
<div class="markdown-alert markdown-alert-important">
<p class="markdown-alert-title">Important</p>
<p>Make sure to install <code>ffmpeg</code> before running the commands provided!</p>
</div>
<p>To install ffmpeg on <strong>Windows</strong> run the following command on the Windows Terminal:</p>
<pre><code class="language-bash">winget install -e --id Gyan.FFmpeg
</code></pre>
<p>To install ffmpeg on <strong>Ubuntu</strong> or derivatives run the following command on terminal:</p>
<pre><code class="language-bash">sudo apt install ffmpeg
</code></pre>
<h2 id="download-in-mp3" tabindex="-1"><a href="https://magoninho.github.io/blog/posts/very-useful-guide-on-yt-dlp/#download-in-mp3" class="header-anchor">Download in MP3</a></h2>
<p>If you want to download a video or a playlist from YouTube and automatically convert it to mp3, run the following command:</p>
<pre><code>yt-dlp &lt;link for video or playlist&gt; -x --audio-format mp3
</code></pre>
<h3 id="downloading-playlist-with-numbered-files" tabindex="-1"><a href="https://magoninho.github.io/blog/posts/very-useful-guide-on-yt-dlp/#downloading-playlist-with-numbered-files" class="header-anchor">Downloading playlist with numbered files</a></h3>
<p>If you want to download a playlist with numbered files like...</p>
<pre><code>01 - File 1.mp3
02 - File 2.mp3
03 - File 3.mp3
...
</code></pre>
<p>...you can run the following command:</p>
<pre><code>yt-dlp -o &quot;%(playlist_index)s - %(title)s.%(ext)s&quot; &lt;link&gt; -x --audio-format mp3
</code></pre>
<h2 id="download-mp4-video" tabindex="-1"><a href="https://magoninho.github.io/blog/posts/very-useful-guide-on-yt-dlp/#download-mp4-video" class="header-anchor">Download MP4 video</a></h2>
<p>If you want to download a video from YouTube in the MP4 format, run the following command:</p>
<pre><code>yt-dlp &lt;link&gt; -S ext
</code></pre>
<h3 id="compatibility-with-video-editors-(like-davinci-resolve)" tabindex="-1"><a href="https://magoninho.github.io/blog/posts/very-useful-guide-on-yt-dlp/#compatibility-with-video-editors-(like-davinci-resolve)" class="header-anchor">Compatibility with video editors (like Davinci Resolve)</a></h3>
<p>If you wish to download videos using <code>yt-dlp</code> and use them in Davinci Resolve, you'll need to recode the video to the MOV format. Thankfully, <code>yt-dlp</code> provides a feature to do so. Just run the following command:</p>
<pre><code>yt-dlp &lt;link&gt; --recode-video mov
</code></pre>
<h2 id="conclusion" tabindex="-1"><a href="https://magoninho.github.io/blog/posts/very-useful-guide-on-yt-dlp/#conclusion" class="header-anchor">Conclusion</a></h2>
<p>In my opinion, these were the most useful commands I could provide</p>
]]>
      </content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://magoninho.github.io/blog/posts/welcome/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://magoninho.github.io/blog/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <content:encoded>
        <![CDATA[<p>I have finally created a blog for myself! I was really looking forward to do so. One of the reasons being that I really wanted to put my english writing skills to the next level. As well as because I recently got a new keyboard, and a mechanical one, and I am really enjoying to type on this thing (I pretend to make a blog post about how typing is very important for programmers). And another good reason is that when I was 10 years old, it was 2015, and everybody had a blog. I really wanted a blog too, so it was like a little dream of mine. This was also another reason for me to start learning to code when I was younger.</p>
<!--more-->
<p>I plan to write about a lot of things in the future. I just have no idea what subject to talk about first lol. I am thinking about maybe writing some simple programming tutorials just like those articles I read on Medium or dev.to. As well as some walkthroughs on how I achieved something like a big project or some job opportunity.</p>
<p>Most of the content will probably be more technical, since I do not have that much experience to talk about more mature content like advices on getting a job (since I am unemployed lol).</p>
]]>
      </content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>